<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Upgrade Quality</name>
  <packageId>rakros.upgradequality</packageId>
  <author>Rakros</author>
  <modVersion>1.5.6</modVersion>
  <modIconPath IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">UpgradeQuality/Icon/ModIcon</modIconPath>
  <url>https://github.com/Gargair/RimWorld_UpgradeQuality</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.4</li>
    <li>1.5</li>
    <li>1.6</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
    <li>MalteSchulze.RIMMSqol</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>Allows to upgrade Quality of everything that has one.
    Upgrading costs a lot of resources and need to be available for upgrading.

    The factor for the costs can be changed in the mod settings. At default they are:
    From awful to poor: 1
    From poor to normal: 2
    From normal to good: 3
    From good to excellent: 4
    From excellent to masterwork: 5
    From masterwork to legendary: 6
    This affects materials and time to build/craft.

    Additionally it is possible to limit the maximum quality a building or item can be upgraded to.
    For items you need to pay special attention, they are limited to the quality of the workbench (can be disabled in options)

    Buildings are upgraded in place. 
    A frame will be placed on top of the building and your colonists will build it like a normal building. 
    Once the frame is finished construction, the building will be upgraded.
    
    Items are upgraded at the upgrade workbench.
    The item filter for the bills will affect the items that will be upgraded.
    The materials required for the upgrade will be decided by the recipe of the item.
    This mod has the same detection mechanism as the base game for the ingredients stat.
    If no recipe is detected as fallback the same item with the same quality is required as ingredient.

    Support for RIMMSqol
    If you change a recipe or building it will be picked up for new upgrades. Already in progress ones still have the old costs.
  </description>
</ModMetaData>